{
    "subject": "resource/Haiku_D'Etat",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Haiku D'Etat was born in United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9275550246238708,
            "question": "What could be some possible reasons for Haiku D'Etat being born in the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8968382477760315,
            "question": "Where was Haiku D'Etat born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6059417724609375,
            "question": "What kind of person is Haiku D'Etat?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5872235298156738,
            "question": "What country is Haiku D'Etat from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47275862097740173,
            "question": "Are there any other notable facts about Haiku D'Etat?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38141191005706787,
            "question": "How is Haiku D'Etat perceived by the public?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3540501594543457,
            "question": "What impact has Haiku D'Etat had on society or culture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3494649827480316,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Haiku D'Etat's upbringing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34774190187454224,
            "question": "Is Haiku D'Etat known for any specific achievements or works?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3024042546749115,
            "question": "Does Haiku D'Etat have any connections to other famous people or events?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Haiku D'Etat was born in United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_523_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Haiku D'Etat known for any specific achievements or works?",
            "html": "dbpedia_523_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Haiku D'Etat's upbringing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_523_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact has Haiku D'Etat had on society or culture?",
            "html": "dbpedia_523_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_523_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_523_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_523_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_523_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_523_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_523_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_523_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_523_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_523_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_523_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{'output': 'yes'} \n\nThe documents mention that \"Haiku d'Etat\" is a super group rap trio featuring Aceyalone and Myka 9 of Freestyle Fellowship and Abstract Rude of Abstract Tribe Unique. This indicates that Haiku D'Etat was formed in the United States, specifically on the West Coast, given the affiliation with Project Blowed and the mention of San Francisco Bay Area musicians."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents describe the formation and members of the group \"Haiku d'Etat,\" which is composed of Aceyalone, Myka 9 (also known as Mikah 9), and Abstract Rude. They are all identified as being from the San Francisco Bay Area, which is in the United States. Therefore, the statement that Haiku D'Etat was born in the United States is supported by the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided context repeatedly mentions  \"Project Blowed,\" \"Bay Area,\" \"San Francisco Bay Area live musicians,\" and \"West Coast underground hip hop.\" All of these indicators strongly suggest a US origin, particularly the California region.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The name \"Haiku d'Etat\" implies a connection to French or European culture, with the term \"coup d'\u00e9tat\" being of French origin.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context mentions that all members of Haiku d'Etat are from the San Francisco Bay Area, which is part of the United States. However, there's no information suggesting any direct connection to a non-U.S. origin for the group itself or its formation outside the U.S.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}